Finding Aid for Gary Shrewsbury photographs, 1983-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Gary Shrewsbury photographs
1983-1990
Shrewsbury, Gary.
2009073 Aa 2
2 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Gary Shrewsbury (donor no. 10047 ) and came to the library in 2008.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open; no duplication of the images is permitted except with the permission of the donor.
Gary Shrewsbury was a contract photographer during the gubernatorial administration of James J. Blanchard, 1983-1990.
The collection consists of photographic negatives of Governor Blanchard while attending public functions, giving speeches, signing bills, and at various other meetings, receptions, political gatherings, and fund raisers.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Blanchard, James J., 1942-; Governors--Michigan.; Michigan. Governor (1983-1991: Blanchard); Michigan--Politics and government--1951-; Michigan--Politics and government--1981-1990.; Shrewsbury, Gary.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- James Blanchard governor
  - Blanchard Inaugural Swearing In, 1/1/1983 (Box 1)
  - Bradmiller, Mt. Pleasant, 5/26/1983 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Youth Corp., 6/1/1983 (Box 1)
  - MSU President, Cecil Mackie, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Youth Corp, 8/17/1983 (Box 1)
  - Speech to Joint Legislature, 10/6/1983 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Merchants Council, 10/19/1983 (Box 1)
  - Workers Compensation, Bill Signing, 12/1983 (Box 1)
  - Income Tax Increase (Box 1)
  - Small Business Week, 5/1984 (Box 1)
  - Small Business Reception, 5/15/1984 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard Residence, G. Mennen Williams, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Chinese Delegation, 8/2/1984 (Box 1)
  - Wharton Center, "Dracula" Reception, 1984 (Box 1)
  - S.O.S. Reception, 1/1984 (Box 1)
  - Education Speech, 2/1984 (Box 1)
  - Commerce Dept., Small Business Week, 5/1984 (Box 1)
  - Bill Signing, Commerce Dept., 7/3/1984 (Box 1)
  - Miss Michigan, 7/3/1984 (Box 1)
  - Bill Signing, 10/2/1984 (Box 1)
  - Press Day, Government Affairs Day, 11/2/1984 (Box 1)
  - Tom Monahan, Small Reception, 11/8/1984 (Box 1)
  - Press Party, 11/27/1984 (Box 1)
  - Small Dinner Reception, 11/1984 (Box 1)
  - Christmas Tree, Quilt Presentation, 12/1984 (Box 1)
  - Committee on Future of Higher Education, 12/1984 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Development Foundation Board-Reception, 12/17/1984 (Box 1)
  - Paula Blanchard-Art, 5/24/1985 (Box 1)
  - Ethnic Festival Signings, 6/5/1985 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard, Bowman Associates, Don Gardner, 7/1/1985 (Box 1)
  - Law Building, Bill Signing, 7/1985 (Box 1)
  - Farm, Bill Signing, 7/1985 (Box 1)
  - Festival Proclamation Signings, 7/1985 (Box 1)
  - Franchise Association 2/1986, Service to the Aging, 3/18/1986 (Box 1)
  - Labor Day, 7/1/1986 (Box 1)
  - Campaign Office, 7/3/1986 (Box 1)
  - Reception, Schlussel Home, 8/1986 (Box 1)
  - With Legislature Candidates-Convention, 8/1986 (Box 1)
  - Paula Blanchard Food Guide, 9/2/1986 (Box 1)
  - Muskegon Fundraiser (Morse Home), 9/9/1986 (Box 1)
  - Paula Blanchard with Kids (Game), 10/1986 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard, G. Mennen Williams Retirement Party, 11/1986 (Box 1)
  - Residence Christmas Tree, 12/1986 (Box 1)
  - Best Bill Signing, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Inauguration, Swearing In Balls 1/1/1987, 1/2/1987 Detroit, 1/3/1987 Grand Rapids (Box 1)
  - Blanchard, Fundraiser with Governor Robb, Gerson Residence, 3/1/1987 (Box 1)
  - New State Police Dir., 5/1987 (Box 1)
  - Reception for Legislators, 5/6/1987 (Box 1)
  - Larry Tokarski Reception, 9/23/1987 (Box 1)
  - Labor Day Reception, 9/7/1987 (Box 1)
  - Larry Glazer Reception, 10/1987 (Box 1)
  - Council on Human Investment, 10/1987 (Box 1)
  - Judge Damon Keith Reception, 10/19/1987 (Box 1)
  - Bishop Airport Expansion, 10/29/1987 (Box 1)
  - NGA Reception, 11/1987 (Box 1)
  - Christmas Tree, 11/30/1987 (Box 1)
  - Friends of the Residence, 12/1987 (Box 1)
  - Press Corp., 12/1987 (Box 1)
  - George Perles Reception, 12/1987 (Box 1)
  - State of the State, 1/20/1988 (Box 1)
  - Blanch and Riegle with Candidates, 8/1988 (Box 1)
  - Single Business Tax Reform, Bill Signing, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard Impression Five Reception, 2/1988 (Box 1)
  - Irish Reception, 3/17/1988 (Box 1)
  - Larry Meyer, "150" Book, 5/1988 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, 4/1988 (Box 1)
  - Labor Luncheon, 5/1988 (Box 1)
  - Corporate Executives Reception, 5/3/1988 (Box 1)
  - Residence, Legislative Reception/Decorations, 5/17/1988 (Box 1)
  - Legislative Reception, 5/18/1988 (Box 1)
  - Convention Delegates, 7/10/1988 (Box 1)
  - Staff Party, 8/1988 (Box 1)
  - Medical Society Luncheon, 9/1988 (Box 1)
  - Women's Commission, 9/1988 (Box 1)
  - Japanese Gov. Signing, 9/1988 (Box 1)
  - Brother-In-Law Reception, 9/1/1988 (Box 1)
  - Reception, Opus 1 Detroit, 9/6/1988 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard-Ticket Sellers, 9/14/1988 (Box 1)
  - Art Council Reception, Oscars, 9/19/1988 (Box 1)
  - Japanese Governor, 9/19/1988 (Box 1)
  - Oakland County Reception, 9/27/1988 (Box 1)
  - Editors and Publishers Reception, 9/30/1988 (Box 1)
  - Macomb County Reception, 10/11/1988 (Box 1)
  - Dukakis/Blanchard Cobo Hall, 10/18/1988 (Box 1)
  - Victory 88 Reception Cobo Hall, 10/18/1988 (Box 1)
  - Wayne County Reception, 10/25/1988 (Box 1)
  - Black Ministers Reception, 12/1988 (Box 1)
  - M.S.U. Reception, 12/1988 (Box 1)
  - Pilots Reception, 12/1988 (Box 1)
  - New State Representatives, 12/1/1988 (Box 1)
  - Larry Meyer 150 Book Christmas Tree, 12/1/1988 (Box 1)
  - OMB, Christmas Reception, 12/6/1988 (Box 1)
  - Press Corp, Rec., 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 1)
  - State of the State Speech, Reception, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Friends of the Residence, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Gary Owen with the Governor, 1/1989 (Box 1)
  - Coffee Mug, Campaign Office Reception, Janet visit to Holt School (Box 1)
  - Jim Pitz Reception, 3/1989 (Box 1)
  - Governor's Reception, Mayor of Dublin, 3/1989 (Box 1)
  - Irish Reception, Detroit, 3/16/1989 (Box 1)
  - Teacher of the Year, 4/1989 (Box 1)
  - Small Dinner Party, 4/1989 (Box 1)
  - Building Trades, 5/8/1989 (Box 1)
  - Small Dinner Party, 5/31/1989 (Box 1)
  - Jimboree Fundraiser, 6/1989 (Box 1)
  - Jimboree, 6/1989 (Box 1)
  - Polish Reception, 6/7/1989 (Box 1)
  - Staff Party Reception, 7/1989 (Box 1)
  - Student Interns, 8/24/1989 (Box 1)
  - Doug Ross Reception, 8/29/1989 (Box 1)
  - State Bar Reception, 9/1989 (Box 1)
  - Italian Reception, 9/1989 (Box 1)
  - Golf Outing, 9/11/1989 (Box 1)
  - Janet's Family, 9/17/1989 (Box 1)
  - Supreme Court Reception, 10/1989 (Box 1)
  - Fundraiser Beggars, 10/1989 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper Reporters/Editors Reception, 10/6/1989 (Box 1)
  - 25th Class Reunion, 10/20/1989 (Box 1)
  - Christmas Tree, 12/4/1989 (Box 1)
  - Fundraiser Miller Residence, Grosse Pointe (Box 2)
  - Christmas Tree/Residence, 12/1989 (Box 2)
  - Blanchard's Sister, Susan and Coworkers, 12/12/1989 (Box 2)
  - End of 89, Beginning of, 1990 (Box 2)
  - State of the State 1990, Lansing Community College, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Conference on Environment, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Governor with Candidates, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Blanchard with Secretary of State Richard Austin (Box 2)
  - Headstart, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Residence, exterior (Box 2)
  - Residence Flavor Garden with Janet (Box 2)
  - Janet Blanchard, Millie Dodak, Pre-State of State Reception, 1/1990 (Box 2)
  - Janet Blanchard's Reception (Box 2)
  - Fundraiser, Dr. Messingers, 1/1990 (Box 2)
  - Democratic Party, Whitney (Box 2)
  - McCarthy Reception, 4/1990 (Box 2)
  - Local Area Chambers of Commerce Reception, 5/1990 (Box 2)
  - Farm Bureau Reception, 7/1990 (Box 2)
  - Roger Smith, 7/1990 (Box 2)
  - Staff Picnic, Residence, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Italian Reception, Dearborn, 10/1990 (Box 2)
  - Irish Reception, Detroit, 10/1990 (Box 2)
  - 30th Class Reunion, 10/11/1990 (Box 2)
  - Dept. Head's Democratic Party, 12/1990 (Box 2)
  - Friends, 12/1990 (Box 2)
  - Staff at Residence, 12/18/1990 (Box 2)
  - Labor Democratic Party, 12/18/1990 (Box 2)
  - Staff Christmas Party, 12/20/1990 (Box 2)
  - Staff, 12/20/1990 (Box 2)
  - Blanchard Portrait Dedication (Box 2)
  - Petting Dog at Dinner Table (Box 2)
  - Jay Blanchard Graduation Party (Box 2)
  - Labor Party (Box 2)
  - Economic Alliance (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
- Governor Blanchard Receptions
  - December 1983-May 1985, 1 volumes
    - Dem County Chairperson, 12/8/1983 (Box 2)
    - Armenians Greeks, 6/19/1984 (Box 2)
    - Italians, 6/28/1984 (Box 2)
    - Irish, 10/2/1984 (Box 2)
    - Hispanics, 10/8/1984 (Box 2)
    - City/County Officials, 12/1984 (Box 2)
    - Martin Taylor Reception, 12/9/1984 (Box 2)
    - Favorites, 12/1984 (Box 2)
    - Agriculture Reception, 4/7/1985 (Box 2)
    - Pro-Choice Reception, 4/18/1985 (Box 2)
    - Wayne County Reception, 4/23/1985 (Box 2)
    - Small Business Reception, 4/29/1985 (Box 2)
    - Consular Corp Reception, 5/16/1985 (Box 2)
    - Oakland County Reception, 5/21/1985 (Box 2)
  - May 1985-July 1985, 1 volumes
    - Arts Award Ceremony, 5/23/1985 (Box 2)
    - Detroit Civic Leaders, 5/28/1985 (Box 2)
    - Detroit Civic Leaders, 5/29/1985 (Box 2)
    - Black Ministers, 6/5/1985 (Box 2)
    - Women's Commission Center for the Arts, 6/11/1985 (Box 2)
    - Macomb County, 6/18/1985 (Box 2)
    - Polish, 6/27/1985 (Box 2)
    - Congressman Gray, 6/9/1985 (Box 2)
    - Ross Perot, E.D.S., 7/11/1985 (Box 2)
    - Sesquicentennial Reception, 7/23/1985 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Foundations, 7/24/1985 (Box 2)
    - Western Michigan, 7/30/1985 (Box 2)